Hi, and this was some I want to talk with you about data privacy and
Especially when we use and hit hub compiler
So please use the website the main web page of the hot copilot
I provided all the links in the resources for this video and if you scroll down
You see frequency ask a question section here, and you can use and you can choose the privacy from the tops by the left side
And you will see the most popular questions. So let's start with the question about what personal data does it have a pilot process
So
You will see that they process some user engagement data. It's of course
Some sewed on an image it inspires like you they not know what the person exactly you would be like
Anonymize a date and provide you some it into fire. So
They process so
Word suggestions or completions you dismiss or accept for example, what are all messages you have?
What are your system logs and some product usage metrics?
But most of the applications process this data. It's it's fine. So you
All of them need to get some information to improve the product quality
The next it's a prompt. So there are some inputs for chat or quote along with the context some context files or like
Project yeah, which send to compile at AI to generate suggestions
they process this data because they need to generate a suggestion to you and
Like I'd know how it's possible without it as
about suggestion. They also process some
Some AI generated quote lines
Like you could have the suggestion for you at base in your prompts and they process also this data
They also process some feedback data from you if you if you if you you know
Using reactions up down fingers about the responses suggestions if you provide some comments or
Even a feedback with support tickets
so but
I call this data should be
anonymously and
Hit cop pilot is the popular question. Does it train on my datum?
They like name this section is
Business or Enterprise and they say no cop pilot does not use easier cop pilot business or Enterprise data to train its model
But a question what about personal plans?
And I have an answer if you open the next link from the resources
It's a cop cop pilot documentation and the model training in improvement section and they tell the bite of all hope
but a cop cop pilot
Give up. It's affiliates and third party companies to do not use your data including your bronze suggestion and cod snippets for AI model training
so
Please relax. Yeah, and this is referred to in your personal settings and your cop cop pilot cannot enable it. So only you can
Like enable the toggle and share your data if you really want it, but by default it's a tablet. So
Don't worry about it
and
Next question. How does it have cop pilot use data?
They use some they use some data to improve the quality of their services to maintain
Add to provide more personal light experience and recommendations
They use it to pick some issues to detect in some security problems or security incidents
To fix in some super bugs and maintain some services
So they also use the might use the data for
Improvuser productivity some quad quality improve privacy and accessibility improvement security even so
And of course some data can be used for building an account management like yo in mail your credit card data
etc
The next question how long could have pertain cop pilot data for business enterprise customers if you use it in IDE or
Chat, so it will like a promise. It's not retain it for user engagement data. They keep it for two years
But if you use on also good cop pilot places, I suppose it's a website probably as a
Pertain prompts and suggestions for 28 dates and user engagement data also keep up to yours. And of course they keep some big data. You send them
Of course they get cop of pilot
Use some data protection agreement and it's GDPR compliant. If you want to use it and you can read the rest of the questions if you want
Also, please visit the link to visit trust center. You can find but almost same questions
But there are some videos which might be also helpful for you about some security
For pilot though, I hope this lesson was useful for you and now you know more about your data privacy and you can I hope to watch
So and see you in the next lessons